cypruscu.com 2017-01-29

# FACTS

                       WHAT DOES CYPRUS CREDIT UNION
FACTS                  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                   Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                       consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                       we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                       understand what we do.
What?                  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                       have with us. This information can include:
                             Name, address, Social Security Number and income
                             Account balances and payment history
                             Account transactions and credit card or other debt
                       When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                       notice.
How?                   All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                       business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                       customers’ personal information; the reasons Cyprus Credit Union chooses to share; and
                       whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                      Does Cyprus Credit
        Reasons we can share your personal information                                       Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                      Union Share?
For our everyday business purposes–
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s),                Yes                        No
respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to
credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes–
To offer our products and services to you                                      Yes                        No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                             Yes                        No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–
Information about your transactions and experiences                            Yes                        No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–
Information about your creditworthiness                                        No                  We do not share
For our affiliates to market to you                                            No                  We do not share
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                             No                  We do not share
Questions?           Call (801) 260-7600, toll-free (800) 929-7787 or go to www.cypruscu.com
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?         Cyprus Credit Union

Page 2
What we do
How does Cyprus Credit        To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
Union protect my              measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards
personal information?         and secured files and buildings.
                              We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who
                              need to know that information to provide products and services to you. Cyprus Credit
                              Union tests and assesses its information security measures, trains employee, and adopts
                              upgrades and enhancements as necessary to protect your information.
How does Cyprus Credit        We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Union collect my personal          Open an account or deposit/withdraw money
information?                       Pay your bills or apply for any service
                                   Provide us information on any online application or transaction, or information
                                      you send to us by email
                                   Use your credit or debit card(s)
                              We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates,
                              or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all         Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing?                           sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your
                                      creditworthiness
                                   affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                   sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                              State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                               Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
                                         and nonfinancial companies.
                                          Cyprus Credit Union has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates                            Companies not related by a common ownership or control. They can be
                                         financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                          Cyprus Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market
                                             to you.
Joint Marketing                          A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                         market financial products or services to you.
                                          Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance and financial
                                             service providers.
Other important information
Cyprus Federal Credit Union does business as Cyprus Credit Union. Cyprus Credit Union reserves the right to amend
this Privacy Statement at any time. The most current copy of the privacy statement is available at www.cypruscu.com.
